{
    "subject": "resource/Fingers_(1978_film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "Fingers (1978 film) is a type of Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.781029462814331,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Fingers'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.647876501083374,
            "question": "Is 'Fingers' a documentary or a fictional film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5861321687698364,
            "question": "What year was the film 'Fingers' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4793804883956909,
            "question": "What is the director of the film 'Fingers'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46752652525901794,
            "question": "What is the general plot of the film 'Fingers'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4254680871963501,
            "question": "What themes are explored in the film 'Fingers'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4137483537197113,
            "question": "What is the critical reception of the film 'Fingers'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3949597179889679,
            "question": "Is there a sequel or prequel to the film 'Fingers'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36638322472572327,
            "question": "Are there any awards associated with the film 'Fingers'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2201901227235794,
            "question": "Can you name any actors who starred in the film 'Fingers'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fingers (1978 film) is a type of Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6451_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any awards associated with the film 'Fingers'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6451_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a sequel or prequel to the film 'Fingers'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6451_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the critical reception of the film 'Fingers'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6451_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6451_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6451_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6451_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6451_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6451_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6451_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6451_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6451_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6451_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6451_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that \"Fingers\" (1978) is indeed a film, directed by James Toback and starring Harvey Keitel. The details about its plot, characters, and production further support this classification as a film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}